

Ravena Auliya Informatics Engineering Student

0895709085454 ravenaauliya@gmail.com Kepulauan Riau, Batam City

SUMMARY

Hi everyone..

My name is Ravena Auliya, my friends often call me Ravena. I am an Informatics Engineering student, Batam State Polytechnic. I started basic web programming in college. I think new knowledge is very interesting to explore. Besides, at this time I learned to focus pursuing experiences that will definitely help me in the future. I can't just wait, I focus on trying.

EXPERIENCE

09/2022 - 12/2022

Front end & Back end

Brail Polibatam Robot Website

Polibatam's robot brail website is a company profile website that aims to convey information about Brail easily and quickly.

- · Project based learning (PBL)
- Front end & Back end main page
- Framework CI 4, PHP 8, Bootstrap

05/2022 - 08/2022

Back end

Tracer Study Alumni

The Tracer Study Alumni application is a data collection and tracking program for alumni based on the CRUD website and MySQL database which aims to find out how much college graduates can be involved in the world of work.

- Mini Project based learning (PBL)
- · Analysis and Alumni page website

EDUCATION

Batam State Polytechnic

D3 - Informatic Engineering

- Active member of informatics engineering association (HMTI), education sector.
- · HMTI FAIR 2022 public relations committee.
- LO KMIPN 2022 committee, PIC in the field of internet of things.

CERTIFICATES

02/2022 - 02/2023

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika (HMTI)

SKILLS

HTML Intermediate CSS Intermediate

JavaScriptBeginnerPHPBeginnerCI 4BeginnerUI/UX DesignBeginner

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Intermediate